I know you had a good year before. Where
do you feel you've really improved as a
pass rusher and what can you bring to
Washington?
>> Um, just knowing my spots. Um,
understanding like the down and
distance, the intensity of the specific
down. Um, understanding like if it's,
you know, runner pass and, you know,
really taking advantage of that and
getting that jump on the count. And then
um you know, like I said, understanding
when you have that one-on-one so you
can, you know, scheme um certain rushes
that you do, you know, go power first
and then, you know, maybe want to change
it up, go speed after that. So, you
know, just playing the game of of pass
rushing. I think I've gotten better at
that.
>> Thank you,
>> Nikki.
>> Hi, Dy. Um what intrigued you about
Washington? Why did you want to sign
here?
>> Um you know, it's close to everything
I've you know, I've I've come to know
growing up. Obviously, I'm growing up in
Jersey. Um, went to school at Penn
State. Um, went to high school in
Jersey. Uh, obviously my first f five
five or so years were in Baltimore. I'm
familiar with the area. U, my sister is
here. So, it's just it just made the
most sense. Um, love the love the people
out here and um, you know, like I said,
made the most sense and I'm glad it
happened.
Sorry, Melissa.
>> Sorry, I didn't know. I didn't know
there. Hi, Daffy. How are you?
>> Melissa, what's up?
>> Good to see you.
>> Um, so obviously up until this point,
you've played in so many different
defensive schemes for, you know, a
handful of coordinators. What do you
feel like you've learned about yourself
and your versatility um throughout these
last five seasons? Um, yeah, just just
that I'm versatile and that um, you
know, if I'm put in any type of
situation, any type of scheme, you know,
I think I'mma find a way or I know I'm
going to find a way to, you know, create
production, but then also at the same
time knowing what I'm good at, um, and,
you know, honing in on that and making
that my strength so that, you know, when
it's time for me to give that for to the
team, I can, you know, impact and, you
know, do a lot and, you know, produce
for for for the team in the right
moments. So, um, I think that's that's
what's really helped me with playing
different schemes, different defensive
coordinators mindsets, just
understanding how they think and playing
to that way, too.
>> David Aldridge.
>> Hey, Adafrey, welcome to DC, man. Um
just wanted to know what specifically um
DQ and Dante said to you and and AP as
well if he was involved in terms of how
they how they think you fit what they're
trying to do and and what you saw from
them what you heard from them that made
you went made you go okay I could work
this could work here. Uh, I mean to be
honest, I left everything to, you know,
my agent and and, you know, the
logistics of everything. But I will say
like once I got here, you know, it was
love and, you know, they really let me
know how they saw me fitting in this
defense in terms of, you know, just
being able to, you know, um, you know,
find those one-on-one matchups and be
able to target those and play fast and,
you know, just play, you know, up the
field. So, um, they let me know that
they were they were going to allow me to
do that and, you know, I was I was on
board with that. You know, I just want
to get after the passer and produce and,
you know, make make big plays for my
team.
>> Ben,
>> hey, uh, Adaf, right?
>> Yes, sir.
>> Okay, great. Um, welcome to town. Um, in
your career, you obviously, you know,
you your athleticism is is obvious. Have
you kind of figured out for you your
your size, what makes the most sense for
you from like a a weight perspective,
muscle perspective, etc. as you kind of
go through the league?
>> Yeah. Yeah, I've kind of try to play
with different weights and have have had
different, you know, outcomes with both
weights. Um, but, um, I think I've had a
good understanding of where I'm at. Um,
I usually find it out towards like the
end of the year, mid mid year, a good,
you know, a good weight that I can still
be fast but still be strong and
explosive. So, you know, I think I I
found that.
>> Donna,
>> hi Adaf, welcome to Washington. In
coming to Washington with the fan base
and your teammates, what is the biggest
thing that you want them to know about
you?
>> Uh, that, you know, I'm going give it my
all. Um, I've been like that since I got
in the league. Um, whether it's, you
know, I'm raw, green, you know, when I
get here, I'm going continue to, you
know, strive to get better and give it
my all every snap. Um, every offseason
I'm going to try to, you know, hone in
on something I can do better from the
past season. And like I said, I'm going
to give it my all. In the crunch moments
that we need, um, a play, that's when
I'm trying to do something. Um, and you
know, I train for that. So, um, that's
the type of player you're going to get
for me. Someone that's just trying to
get better and continue to excel and,
um, you know, just just help the team
win.
>> Awesome. All right. Appreciate it.
>> Appreciate y'all.
>> Thank you.
Congratulations.
Appreciate it.